PINE HILLS FORTNIGHTLY CLUB, INC. RECORDS (APAP031) 1898-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Papers Presented, 1911-1984; 6; 0.78
  - "Recollecting the Great Depression", by Charity Roth, 1998 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Letchworth State Park", by Vera Scadura, 1998 November 23 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "Poets", by Dories Welish, 1999 November 12 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Stamp Collecting", by Vera Scadura, 2000 January 10 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "The Isle of Man", by Eleanor Lattimer, 2000 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Aleutian Islands", by Vera Scadura, 2001 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Population Control in China: Where have all the flowers gone?" by Joan Taylor, 2002 January 14 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "Contemporary Chinese Music and Dance", by Eleanor Clarke, 2002 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "Profits and Problems: U.S.-China Trade", by Vera Scadura, 2002 March 25 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Some Governors who Lived in the Mansion", by Anne Roberts, 2002 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Cat-tails: From Deification to Demonization", by Joan Taylor, 2003 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Programs, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Papers Presented having undated and/or no author, 6.88
    - "North Carolina's Delegates to the Constitutional Convention", by Evelyn Jenkins, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - no author - "Alexander Hamilton--First American Business Man", Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - no author - "All Gaul is divided...", Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - no author - "American Architecture", Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - no author - "Author: Winifred Holtby", Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - no author - "Background of the Constitution", Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - no author - "Miracle at Philadelphia", Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - no author - "Mormonism", Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - no author - "New Hope For Iran", Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - no author - "Novel:The Mother", Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - no author - "Once Upon a Time--in a Kingdom by the Sea", Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - no author - "Opening Utopian Gates", Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - no author - "Rhode Island Food", Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - no author - "Poland", Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - no author - "The Triangle Fire: It's (sic) Effect on Women's Working Conditions 1910-20", Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - no author - "Washington Irving--Chronicler of the Hudson", Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - no author - "Genealogy", Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - no author - "1920-1930: The Third Decade of the Twentieth Century", Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - "Lindbergh Episode", by Alice Hastings Murphy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)